<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Bethel University Staff and Faculty Openings</title>
        <description>A listing of the current staff and faculty openings at Bethel University</description>
        <link>https://www.bethel.edu/employment/</link>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Master Electrician</title>
            <description>Maintain the electrical and lighting systems throughout the college campus to provide safe, efficient and comfortable environment for students, staff and guests. Insures diagnosis and correction of problems and issues as they occur. </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2018-1219</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1219/master-electrician/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Senior Systems Administrator</title>
            <description>Leads the evaluation of existing systems and technologies and development of strategic solutions, documenting relevant deployment models or views that show how the current and future needs of Bethel University’s IT infrastructure will be met in an efficient, sustainable, agile, and adaptable manner. </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1328</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1328/senior-systems-administrator/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Director of Student Activities &amp; Campus Engagement</title>
            <description>Develop and provide oversight to the Bethel University College of Arts &amp; Sciences (CAS) student programming including, but not limited to oversight of Bethel Student Government, oversight of the Loft space in Brushaber Commons and co-advising administratively for the Clarion student newspaper. Share responsibilities with Student Life deans for mentoring, discipline, and assisting students with personal and education related issues.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1330</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1330/director-of-student-activities-%26-campus-engagement/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Assistant Men&#39;s Hockey Coach/Assistant Rec Sports Supervisor/Club Liason</title>
            <description>Assist the Head Coach as requested in recruiting, training and coaching members of the sport team. The assistant coach is expected to mentor student athletes in their holistic development, including nurturing their spiritual formation, giving attention to their physical well-being, monitoring their academic progress, and facilitating a team culture that produces vitality resulting in a high level of student athlete satisfaction and competitive success. Assist in overseeing all functions of the Rec Sports program.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1332</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1332/assistant-men%27s-hockey-coach-assistant-rec-sports-supervisor-club-liason/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Enrollment Counselor</title>
            <description>Recruits new and/or returning students for Bethel University through identifying, qualifying, and cultivating prospective students. </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1334</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1334/enrollment-counselor/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Residence Life Administrative Assistant</title>
            <description>The Residence Life Administrative Assistant will work with the Housing Specialist to organize several housing and residence life processes; develop an expert knowledge of housing software and provide departmental support for administrative processes.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1336</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1336/residence-life-administrative-assistant/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Assistant Dean for Residence Life</title>
            <description>This is a live-in position. Responsible for supervising and supporting the RD staff, their duties and the residents in their areas. Foster a positive, safe and educational residential environment for all students by facilitating community, offering direction to programming, and journeying with students through crisis, community standard infractions and personal and spiritual development</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1338</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1338/assistant-dean-for-residence-life/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Transfer Evaluation Specialist</title>
            <description>Responsible for managing a comprehensive system of transfer evaluations for prospective and current students.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1339</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1339/transfer-evaluation-specialist/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Graduate Assistant Coach in Men&#39;s Basketball</title>
            <description>Assist the Head Coach as requested in coaching, training and recruiting members of the sport team.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1342</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1342/graduate-assistant-coach-in-men%27s-basketball/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Graduate Assistant Coach in Women&#39;s Basketball</title>
            <description>Assist the Head Coach as requested in coaching, training and recruiting members of the sport team.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1343</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1343/graduate-assistant-coach-in-women%27s-basketball/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>3rd Shift Nightwatch Custodian</title>
            <description>Support the mission and values of Bethel University by performing custodial and security services to the academic buildings.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1337</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1337/3rd-shift-nightwatch-custodian/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Human Resources Assistant</title>
            <description>Responsible for the support of day-to-day human resources operations.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1344</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1344/human-resources-assistant/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Manager, Human Resources Operations</title>
            <description>Responsible for the overall strategic oversight and administration of employee benefits, payroll, and human resources information systems functions.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1345</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1345/manager%2c-human-resources-operations/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Administrative Assistant</title>
            <description>Provide administrative support to the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and Chief Diversity Officer (CDO), and their respective offices and backup support to the Executive Vice President and Provost. </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1348</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1348/administrative-assistant/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Student Success Advisor</title>
            <description>Responsible for providing a first point of contact for student counsel and support in both curricular and co-curricular domains, and for the proactive cultivation of substantive relationships with students for the purpose of supporting their overall success through the completion of their academic program.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1349</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1349/student-success-advisor/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Transfer Evaluation Specialist</title>
            <description>Serves as point of contact for transfer evaluation and prior learning assessment.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1350</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1350/transfer-evaluation-specialist/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Student Success Advisor</title>
            <description>Responsible for providing a first point of contact for student counsel and support in both curricular and co-curricular domains, and for the proactive cultivation of substantive relationships with students for the purpose of supporting their overall success through the completion of their academic program.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1353</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1353/student-success-advisor/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Resident Hall Custodian</title>
            <description>Perform duties of a custodian, as well as others duties related to Facilities Management operations as assigned by the Housing Lead Supervisor and the Manager of Building Services. </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1351</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1351/resident-hall-custodian/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Resident Hall Custodian</title>
            <description>Perform duties of a custodian, as well as others duties related to Facilities Management operations as assigned by the Housing Lead Supervisor and the Manager of Building Services. </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1352</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1352/resident-hall-custodian/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>ITS Project Manager</title>
            <description>Responsible for all project phases (Initiate, Plan, Execute, Monitor &amp; Control and Close) to deliver accurate and consistent Information Technology Services projects. </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1354</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1354/its-project-manager/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Head Men&#39;s Golf Coach</title>
            <description>Responsible for recruiting, training, and coaching members of the men’s golf team. The head coach is expected to mentor student athletes in their holistic development, including nurturing their spiritual formation, giving attention to their physical wellbeing, monitoring their academic progress, and facilitating a team culture that produces vitality resulting in a high level of student athlete satisfaction and competitive success.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1355</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1355/head-men%27s-golf-coach/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Administrative Project and Planning Coordinator</title>
            <description>Provide administrative support, coordination and day-to-day management for CIO and Information Technology Services.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1356</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1356/administrative-project-and-planning-coordinator/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>BUILD Residential Supervisor- Year One &amp; Year Two</title>
            <description>To oversee the residential components of the BUILD program, supervise Housing Mentors, and assist with community and independent living skill development as well as conflict management. Currently has two open positions (One for Year 1 students and the other for Year 2 students). The is a Live on-campus position.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1358</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1358/build-residential-supervisor--year-one-%26-year-two/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Associate Dean for Intercultural Programs (ICP) College of Arts &amp; Sciences</title>
            <description>Provides leadership and oversight of programs and services to support multicultural students in their social, academic, and spiritual growth. Works in close collaboration with the Chief Diversity Officer and the Office of Student Life to provide educational opportunities for all students to foster and nurture holistic, integrated, cross-cultural community life at Bethel University.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1359</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1359/associate-dean-for-intercultural-programs-%28icp%29-college-of-arts-%26-sciences/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Internship Supervisor- Year-One</title>
            <description>Provides oversight of year-one internships to the BUILD program in conjunction with the director to ensure that students are able to successfully fulfill the requirements for an Applied Studies Certificate. Manage daily operations related to BUILD program focus on developing employment skills through internship work experiences including working with employers to arrange internships, developing and teaching BUILD Internship lab and year-one Internship and Jobs and Employment Courses, hiring, training, and supervising job mentors, as well as designing and implementing personalized learning process to track student progress in development of employment skills.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1357</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1357/internship-supervisor--year-one/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Athletic Trainer</title>
            <description>The athletic trainer works under the supervision of the director of athletic training services and supervises the care of student athletes competing in the University’s athletic program. The athletic trainer is responsible for the prevention, evaluation, management and rehabilitation of injuries within the University’s comprehensive sports medicine program. Athletic Trainers also serve as Preceptors as part of a CAATE accredited Athletic Training program.  We currently have 3 open positions.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1360</guid>
            <link>https://staffcareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1360/athletic-trainer/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Adjunct Faculty- College of Arts and Sciences</title>
            <description>Adjunct faculty members are an important part of our academic programs. Thank you for your interest in supporting Bethel’s commitment to provide high quality learning experiences for our students. </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2017-1057</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1057/adjunct-faculty--college-of-arts-and-sciences/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Social Work Faculty (Tenure Track)/Field Director</title>
            <description>The Department of Social Work invites qualified candidates to apply for a full-time, tenure-track BSW faculty position that includes undergraduate teaching in the Social Work department, field director responsibilities, academic advising, and institutional service.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1314</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1314/social-work-faculty-%28tenure-track%29-field-director/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Nursing Faculty</title>
            <description>Teaching responsibilities include clinical, laboratory, and/or theory courses working with students in the traditional baccalaureate nursing program. A clinical specialty with relevant clinical experience is necessary; clinical experience in medical/surgical nursing preferred. General faculty responsibilities include involvement in the activities of the department, for example, student advising, participation in teaching teams, and committees.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1340</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1340/nursing-faculty/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Adjunct Faculty - MBA with Healthcare Administration</title>
            <description>This adjunct teaching position is in the Graduate School teaching MBA students in a Healthcare Administration concentration.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2018-1297</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1297/adjunct-faculty---mba-with-healthcare-administration/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Counseling Faculty (Tenure Track)</title>
            <description>This is a full-time faculty position in the Graduate School (GS) teaching M.A. in Counseling students in the specialty area of Clinical Mental Health Counseling.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2018-1289</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1289/counseling-faculty-%28tenure-track%29/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Adjunct Faculty - College of Adult &amp; Professional Studies</title>
            <description> Teach one or more courses in the College of Adult &amp; Professional Studies as assigned by program director.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2017-1024</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1024/adjunct-faculty---college-of-adult-%26-professional-studies/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Adjunct Faculty - Graduate School</title>
            <description>Teach one or more courses in the College of Adult &amp; Professional Studies and/or Graduate School as assigned by program director.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2017-1058</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1058/adjunct-faculty---graduate-school/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Program Director, Doctorate of Physical Therapy</title>
            <description>Bethel University seeks an innovative, experienced leader to serve as the founding program director of Bethel’s planned Doctorate of Physical Therapy program. The program director will lead the design, development, launch, and growth of a successful, high-quality Doctorate in Physical Therapy program. This person must be knowledgeable about and responsible for program organization, administration, fiscal management, continuous review and analysis, planning, development, and participation in the accreditation process.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2017-1097</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1097/program-director%2c-doctorate-of-physical-therapy/job</link>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>