<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Bethel University Faculty Openings</title>
        <description>A listing of the current faculty openings at Bethel University</description>
        <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/search</link>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Adjunct Faculty- College of Arts and Sciences</title>
            <description>Adjunct faculty members are an important part of our academic programs. Thank you for your interest in supporting Bethel’s commitment to provide high quality learning experiences for our students. </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2017-1057</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1057/adjunct-faculty--college-of-arts-and-sciences/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Social Work Faculty (Tenure Track)/Field Director</title>
            <description>The Department of Social Work invites qualified candidates to apply for a full-time, tenure-track BSW faculty position that includes undergraduate teaching in the Social Work department, field director responsibilities, academic advising, and institutional service.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1314</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1314/social-work-faculty-%28tenure-track%29-field-director/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Nursing Faculty</title>
            <description>Teaching responsibilities include clinical, laboratory, and/or theory courses working with students in the traditional baccalaureate nursing program. A clinical specialty with relevant clinical experience is necessary; clinical experience in medical/surgical nursing preferred. General faculty responsibilities include involvement in the activities of the department, for example, student advising, participation in teaching teams, and committees.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2019-1340</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1340/nursing-faculty/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Adjunct Faculty - MBA with Healthcare Administration</title>
            <description>This adjunct teaching position is in the Graduate School teaching MBA students in a Healthcare Administration concentration.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2018-1297</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1297/adjunct-faculty---mba-with-healthcare-administration/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Counseling Faculty (Tenure Track)</title>
            <description>This is a full-time faculty position in the Graduate School (GS) teaching M.A. in Counseling students in the specialty area of Clinical Mental Health Counseling.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2018-1289</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1289/counseling-faculty-%28tenure-track%29/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Adjunct Faculty - College of Adult &amp; Professional Studies</title>
            <description> Teach one or more courses in the College of Adult &amp; Professional Studies as assigned by program director.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2017-1024</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1024/adjunct-faculty---college-of-adult-%26-professional-studies/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Adjunct Faculty - Graduate School</title>
            <description>Teach one or more courses in the College of Adult &amp; Professional Studies and/or Graduate School as assigned by program director.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2017-1058</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1058/adjunct-faculty---graduate-school/job</link>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Program Director, Doctorate of Physical Therapy</title>
            <description>Bethel University seeks an innovative, experienced leader to serve as the founding program director of Bethel’s planned Doctorate of Physical Therapy program. The program director will lead the design, development, launch, and growth of a successful, high-quality Doctorate in Physical Therapy program. This person must be knowledgeable about and responsible for program organization, administration, fiscal management, continuous review and analysis, planning, development, and participation in the accreditation process.</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate>
            <guid>2017-1097</guid>
            <link>https://facultycareers-bethel.icims.com/jobs/1097/program-director%2c-doctorate-of-physical-therapy/job</link>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>